# MUHAMMAD MUQRRAB

WEB DEVELOPER



**2** 0317-7671818

muqrrab2@gmail.com

Manzoor Park, St. No. 10

### PROFILE

I am Muqrrab and have 2 years of experience in full stack web development in Asp.Net and Django. My expertise includes both Front and Backend Development. I have created many sites locally. I am applying to intern as a backend developer.

# SKILLS

- Full Stack Web Design
- Front End development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Js, ReactJs)
- Backend development (Asp.Net MVC (C#), Django)
- APIs Integration
- MsSql Database Integration
- Strong Communication

## EDUCATION

#### **BS COMPUTER SCIENCE**

National Textile universirty 2020 - 2024 3.58 - CGPA

### **INTERMEDIATE**

Superior Group of Colleges 2018-2020 918/1100

### EXPERIENCE

### WEB DEVELOPMENT

Freelancing

2020 - Present

- Database administration and website design
- Both Frontend and Backend Development
- Complete Ecommerce and business sites

### **MSSQL DATABASE**

### 2020-Present

- Database administration
- Built the logic

#### ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

Freelancing

### 2019-Present

- Creating Products images for Ecommerce sites
- Making Menus for restaurants
- Making flyers and Banners